{
    "subject": "resource/Niels-Henning_\u00d8rsted_Pedersen",
    "predicate": "property/associatedActs",
    "object": "resource/Jean-Luc_Ponty",
    "human_readable": "Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen was associated with Jean-Luc Ponty.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9767757654190063,
            "question": "Were Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen and Jean-Luc Ponty collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9682998061180115,
            "question": "Who was Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9193737506866455,
            "question": "What instruments did Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen and Jean-Luc Ponty play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9100908041000366,
            "question": "Did Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen and Jean-Luc Ponty have a long-lasting professional relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870212435722351,
            "question": "In what musical genre did both Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen and Jean-Luc Ponty work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633723855018616,
            "question": "Can you name any other musicians who worked with both Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen and Jean-Luc Ponty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6183794736862183,
            "question": "What is Jean-Luc Ponty known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.038701266050338745,
            "question": "Were there any notable performances or recordings featuring both musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02278199978172779,
            "question": "What impact did their collaboration have on the music scene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01814635656774044,
            "question": "What period in musical history marked their collaboration?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen was associated with Jean-Luc Ponty.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6851_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did their collaboration have on the music scene?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6851_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable performances or recordings featuring both musicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6851_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jean-Luc Ponty known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6851_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6851_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen is a legendary bass player who, along with Wolfgang Dauner and Daniel Humair, completes Ponty's quartet on the album \"Sunday Walk\". This indicates an association between Jean-Luc Ponty and Niels-Henning \u00d8rsted Pedersen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}